Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XVIII is arranged in 5 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XVIII. DISTRICT COUNCILS
  - Sub-Series 224-0. District Councils
    - General, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      1960-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 224-5. District Councils
    - Chicago, 1958-1962 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      1958-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 224-9. District Councils
    - Lodge Charters. General, 1955-1959 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      Feb. 1955-Dec. 1959.
  - Sub-Series 224-10. District Councils
    - East St. Louis-St. Louis Joint Council of Lodges (Dissolved, Effective June 25, 1964), 1948-1964 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 224-21. District Councils
    - Memphis (Disbanded Nov. 16, 1967), 1940-1967 (Box 69, Folder 15)